// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q003: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Streamlining the textile production process has resulted in an ------ 20 percent increase in productivity.',
      choices: ['apparently', 'approximately', 'affordably', 'efficiently'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['approximately'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q021',
    },
    {
      question: 'Mr. Hunter, who joined the company only three months ago, was able to find the cause of the machine’s breakdown ------.',
      choices: ['his own', 'him', 'he', 'himself'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['himself'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q022',
    },
    {
      question: 'Garbage collection in the Carson area is twice a week, on Mondays and Thursdays, unless there is a ------ reason.',
      choices: ['specialize', 'specialist', 'specially', 'special'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['special'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q023',
    },
    {
      question: 'Those who book a room through the San Remo Inn website will receive ------ breakfast.',
      choices: ['complimentary', 'reluctant', 'prominent', 'renewable'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['complimentary'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q024',
    },
    {
      question: 'Visitors must carry their entry passes at all times when ------ the factory’s facilities.',
      choices: ['tour', 'toured', 'will tour', 'touring'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['touring'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q025',
    },
    {
      question: 'Delmar Auto Industries has signed a contract to purchase electronic components from Stellar Corporation ------after lengthy negotiations.',
      choices: ['periodical', 'periodically', 'period', 'periodic'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['periodically'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q026',
    },
    {
      question: 'To enter Lipton National Park on weekends, tickets must be reserved online in ------.',
      choices: ['short', 'person', 'progress', 'advance'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['advance'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q027',
    },
    {
      question: 'Thompson Manufacturing is known in the agricultural machinery industry as a ------ manufacturer of machine parts.',
      choices: ['reliability', 'reliable', 'rely', 'reliably'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['reliable'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q028',
    },
    {
      question: 'Since the main roads in the center of the city are congested during the summer festival, people ------ to use public transportation.',
      choices: ['encouraged', 'are encouraged', 'encourage', 'have encouraged'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['are encouraged'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q029',
    },
    {
      question: 'Heavy snowfall since last night has ------ significant delays in the arrival of flights from Sapporo.',
      choices: ['led', 'resulted', 'included', 'caused'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['caused'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題021-030/#q030',
    },
  ],
}